<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-08-20T19:05:35+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">MLIT</title><subtitle>Welcome to MyLifeInTech, a tech blog by Ndcharles Nweke on Data, Tech and its Products.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">I was at CSA Africa 2022, UNILAG</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/csa-africa-2022/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I was at CSA Africa 2022, UNILAG" /><published>2022-08-12T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-08-12T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/csa-africa-2022</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/csa-africa-2022/"><![CDATA[<p>I attended <a href="https://www.csaafrica.org/csaafrica-2022">Computer Science Academy Africa 2022</a>, hosted by <a href="https://twitter.com/soolaosebikan">
Sofiat Olaosebikan</a> and her wonderful <a href="https://www.csaafrica.org/team">team</a> at <a href="https://twitter.com/nithub_lag">NitHub, UNILAG</a> and this is what I learned.</p>

<p>At first, while I was applying and saw the option asking about your University, I thought I won’t be selected (I’m already graduated). I filled it anyway and forgot about it until… well, I received the Congratulations email.</p>

<p>There were a lot of promises made to participants that I was so eager to attend. Free lunch, accommodation and three weeks of constant drills in python, data structures, machine learning and IoT plus an opportunity to meet undergrads and grads alike. That sounds like a lot but the experience was worth it.</p>

<h2 id="why-was-i-there">Why was I there?</h2>

<p>There is something I always believed about having enough information to get you ahead. And the need to connect with people going your way (on the same journey as you). CSA Africa was an avenue for me to explore programming beyond the confines of me and online tutorials. It was a means to learn and connect with people (beginners and experienced alike) in the tech space, meet amazing roomies I made friends out of and another I found a tech co-founder in – just kidding.</p>

<p>Well, I met people who were good at what they do. Those who were in other walks of life but understood the use of programming in their future ambitions. I also met people who think far into the future and needed help grabbing that future by its horn.</p>

<h2 id="further-programming-experience">Further programming experience.</h2>

<p>Our first day at CSAA was an awesomely scary experience that it made me question if I ever learnt to actually program in Python. Unfortunately not. I trained mostly using videos, and textbooks and hearing Stephen speak of recursion and memoisation made me realise that there is a lot I have to learn to fully equip my Python toolbox for what is coming.</p>

<p>During our first class on recursion, I recalled my very first task at work which involved a deeply nested JSON dictionary. I found it difficult untangling it and although a friend helped with some parts of it, I now realised recursion/mnemonic is best suited to such problems.</p>

<p>The first week of CSA Africa took us through different further programming tasks in Python. Haven refreshed our memories on the basics (lists, dictionaries, slicing and more) we dived into recursions, memoisation and functional programming (lambda, map, reduce and filter).</p>

<p>Up until now, I have written progrmas around functions. You know, block of statements which manipulate data. This is what is called procedural programming. At CSA Africa, we went further into object-oriented programming (OOP). It involves combining data and functionality and wrapping it using classes and objects. (<a href="https://www.tutorialspoint.com/differences-between-procedural-and-object-oriented-programming">Here are their differences</a>)</p>

<h2 id="the-machine-learning-experience">The Machine Learning Experience</h2>
<p>My first attempt to do machine learning with just Numpy and no Pandas was at CSA. It was frustrating at first but then, it was an experience I really enjoyed. And when you think that was all there is, we had to implement the KNN and KMeans algorithms from scratch. Besides, learning about classification, regression and clustering algorithms, we also learned to evaluate our model outputs.</p>

<h2 id="projects">Projects</h2>

<p>I had a wonderful group. Although starting off was challenging, we found a way to kick-off and get the project going. We settled for a laptop price prediction project. (Original dataset <a href="https://github.com/Raghavagr/Laptop_Price_Prediction/blob/main/laptop_data.csv">here</a>).</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/ndcharles/csa_africa/blob/main/project/laptop_data.csv">Given the dataset</a> with several attributes, we performed several cleaning operations on it (<a href="https://github.com/ndcharles/csa_africa/blob/main/project/ml_laptop_cleaned.csv">see the cleaned version here</a>) and then built a machine learning model to predict the price of laptops.</p>

<p>The project isn’t grandiose, but we learnt what we needed to while executing it.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>We didn’t change the world, but we took a step further into changing the world.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Our team lead <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">(@tife)</code> stayed up till 1:00 am trying to perfect our PowerPoint presentation. He confessed to learning a lot from that experience.  <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Maradeben</code>, was busy trying different models, even after we have saved our models to file, looking to improve our model from 89% accuracy score to 90-something. He succeeded in getting to 98% (although we didn’t end up using it due to technical constraints of his implementation). <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Omotayo</code> was there trying to grasp the whole concept of ML (he will catch-up soon). And here I am, sharing the experience with you. I had exposure to ML, so I took it further to get the team to implement a FastAPI backend for our project.</p>

<p>You can <a href="https://github.com/ndcharles/csa_africa/tree/main/project">checkout our project files here</a>.</p>

<p>I can go ahead and tell you about other groups, from implementing algorithms based on stable marriage (e shock you ba?) to seeing the beginners class build amazing stuffs using Python and Tkinter.</p>

<h2 id="overall-experience">Overall Experience</h2>

<p>In the end, if you ask me, “How was CSA Academy 2022 bootcamp?”
Ok. I should probably rephrase that question to the way <a href="https://twitter.com/vodumuyiwa">Dr. Olumuyiwa</a> puts it, “Minus the food, how was the CSAA 2022 bootcamp?”. 🌝</p>

<p>I would, without further ado say, “it was amazing.”</p>

<p>It was an inclusive experience that ensured you learnt something within the short duration we all spent together. I know, right?</p>

<p>A close pal during the bootcamp would say UNILAG likes PR but… so far as we were properly accommodated during the CSAA event, wetin concern me and your intentions.</p>

<p>The hostel experience was nice with enough electricity and water to justify the reasons we left our homes for the provided accommodation. I don’t know about everyone else but I opted for accommodation for several reasons. One of which was to avoid the everyday Lagos stress as I commute between the Bootcamp and my house; I know I won’t learn enough. I also needed to connect with other learners, which won’t be possible if I were stuck trying to rush home after each day. Electricity can be unfavourable in my area, so let’s not go there.</p>

<h2 id="next-steps">Next Steps</h2>

<p>As CSA Academy 2022 has come to an end, a couple of things and further steps are clear to me:</p>

<ul>
  <li>
    <p>To improve further my Python programming skills bearing in mind the tools introduced to me. I also got a glimpse of data structures and algorithms since my roomies were in that track. This is something I would also explore further, especially the time and space complexity problem.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>I got a renewed energy to deep dive into my machine learning studies; with respect to the theoretical aspects of things. Why do you choose this model over that? How do you explain what your model is doing to a lay person? I believe that is the beginning of building and working with explainable machine learning models.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Truly, getting out to meet people helps you understand others and most especially, you. I met wonderful people and connected with a few of them. People are going through different things. Everyone simply devises a way to cope with the challenges of growing up to become a meaningful human. No one’s got it worse, you just have it in a different measure.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Aside from the seriousness, CSAA has set a very high standard for other bootcamps I would be attending in the future. They understood and showed that the comfort of a learner is as important as the actual learning.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>But then, we have every little opportunity to influence people within our sphere. I plan to do that henceforth.</p>
  </li>
</ul>

<p>Thank you CSA Africa, and a big one to NitHub for being so awesome.</p>

<p><iframe style="width:100%;" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RNXhsZcvLtA?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>

<blockquote>
  <p>To the friends and acquaintances I made during these few weeks and to those I never got to meet, better days ahead.</p>
</blockquote>

<p><strong>P.S:</strong> “Love and legacy are the sacrifices we make for progress.” ✌️</p>

<p>Image source: <a href="https://twitter.com/CSAcademyAfrica">CSA Africa on Twitter</a></p>]]></content><author><name>ndcharles</name></author><category term="Data" /><category term="Tech" /><category term="sticky" /><category term="csa_africa_2022" /><category term="python_bootcamp" /><category term="NitHub" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I attended Computer Science Academy Africa 2022, hosted by Sofiat Olaosebikan and her wonderful team at NitHub, UNILAG and this is what I learned.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/csa_africa_2022.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/csa_africa_2022.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Product Analytics: How to Use Data to Build Products that Customers Need</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/cxl-product-analytics-how-data-build-products-customers-need/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Product Analytics: How to Use Data to Build Products that Customers Need" /><published>2022-04-05T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2022-04-05T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/cxl-product-analytics-how-data-build-products-customers-need</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/cxl-product-analytics-how-data-build-products-customers-need/"><![CDATA[<p>At the beginning of most products, instincts, gut-feeling, interviews and surveys form the basis of decision making. After developement and people start using the product, data is generated. The available data is then used to validate hypothesis that would help in improving the product. This is when product analytics comes in.</p>

<p>I work in an ecommerce company and although, most conversations around product analytics tend to gear towards product-led companies, ecommerce can also take advantage of the product analytics journey.</p>

<h2 id="what-is-product-analytics">What is Product Analytics?</h2>

<blockquote>
  <p>Product analytics show you who your users are, what they want, and how to keep them.
<cite>—<a href="https://amplitude.com/behavioral-analytics-platform">Amplitude</a></cite></p>
</blockquote>

<p>Product analytics refers to capturing and analyzing quantitative data through embedded tools that record how users interact with a product. It is about using data to understand who your users are, how they use your product and how these affects your business.</p>

<p>Product Analytics can answer different types of questions ranging from trends to analyzing feature adoption or engagement over time, to visualizing intricate experiences and user flows inside or outside the product.</p>

<h2 id="why-is-product-analytics-important">Why is product analytics important?</h2>
<p>Product analytics allow companies to fully understand how users engage with what they build. It is especially useful for technology products where teams can track users’ digital footprints step-by-step to see what they like or dislike and what leads them to engage, return, or churn.</p>

<h2 id="how-to-implement-product-analytics">How to implement product analytics</h2>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Step 1: Define your business goals</strong></li>
</ul>

<p>The first step is defining a clear-cut business objectives that you want to optimize using data. Then you can ask the right questions like how many people used the wishlist feature last month?, what percentage of users used the skin expert feature last month compared to this month?</p>

<p>To create good set of questions that accurately matches the data you have to your business goals, you should consider using the Product Analytics Question framework below by Matthew.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/product_analytics_question_framework.jpg" alt="product_analytics_question_framework" /></p>

<p>Example questions using the framework;</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/product_analytics_question_framework_example1.jpg" alt="product_analytics_question_framework_example1" /></p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/product_analytics_question_framework_example2.jpg" alt="product_analytics_question_framework_example2" /></p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Step 2: Create a tracking plan</strong></li>
</ul>

<p>Creating an analytics tracking plan helps us to collect the right amount of and correct data to cover our business use case. Incorrect data can lead to incorrect metrics and further misleading conclusions that end up marring the business decisions made from our conclusions.</p>

<p>A tracking plan is an Excel or Google Spreadsheet that contains all the events and properties that you would like to track. An event is simply an action that a user takes (e.g. signing up for your product, uploading a picture or adding a product to cart). Properties are attributes attached to each event (e.g. when a user signs up for our product we would like to know their userID, dateOfSubscription, subscriptionPlan (free or paid) and so on).</p>

<hr />
<h4 id="what-do-we-track">What do we track?</h4>
<p>Anything that happens within our product e.g. button clicks, screen views.</p>

<h4 id="data-scopes">Data scopes</h4>
<p>Data scope tells us how data is put together.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/data_scopes.jpg" alt="data_scopes" />
<em>A single user can have multiple sessions, and each session can have multiple hits, as illustrated above.</em></p>

<ul>
  <li>Users: Anyone interacting with your product is a user. Example user metric include, days since last session, monthly active users, feature adoption rate, etc.</li>
  <li>Session: Interactions by a single user are grouped into sessions. Example session metric is bounce rate.</li>
  <li>Events (or hits) is a collection of all interactions that happened during a session. Example event metrics include pageviews and video plays.</li>
</ul>

<h4 id="properties">Properties</h4>

<ul>
  <li>User properties: A user has properties that are automatically captured by the analytics tool (e.g. location based on IP address, device used) or manually defined by you (e.g. user’s age, type of user).</li>
  <li>Event properties: Events also have properties. Although they aren’t used as often as user properties, they capture valuable metadata about the event itself (e.g. message sent from driver to rider is the first time they are messaging) or state of the user when the event was generated (e.g., Jane was 21 years old when she registered a year ago but is now 22).</li>
</ul>

<hr />

<p>To develop a tracking plan we; define key events, decide what context you need for them and then determine what we need to know about our users.</p>

<p><img src="https://help.mixpanel.com/hc/article_attachments/360036938031/Implementation_Spec_Part2.png" alt="sample_tracking_plan" />
<em>A sample tracking plan from Mixpanel (for full image, open in new tab)</em></p>

<p>For a comprehensive guide on creating a tracking plan, with templates you can use as inspiration, <a href="https://help.mixpanel.com/hc/en-us/articles/115004519886-Do-you-have-industry-specific-tracking-plans-I-can-use-">read this article</a>.</p>

<h3 id="datalayer">DataLayer</h3>

<p>DataLayer is a way to store semantic metadata based on users, sessions, products, content etc. We use it to create an easy way to access information on the website. DataLayers are used instead of scraping because they (dataLayers) are more reliable and don’t change as often as the website’s code.</p>

<h3 id="what-makes-a-good-datalayer">What makes a good dataLayer?</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Tool-agnostic: It should be created for the sole purpose and not tied to a particular tool. e.g. <em>userID</em> <strong>NOT</strong> <em>GAUserID</em>.</li>
  <li>Generic: It should be able to satisfy several use cases. e.g. <em>currentPlanName</em> <strong>NOT</strong> <em>proPlanSubscriber</em> and;</li>
  <li>Consistent: Variable names should follow a naming convention and also be usable in different cases.</li>
</ul>

<p>DataLayer helps us to debug our tracking setup and as well provides us with reliable and readily accessible values for reporting.</p>

<p><strong>Also see:</strong> How I created an <a href="/ecommerce-datalayer">eCommerce Website DataLayer</a>.</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Step 3: Choose the right analytics tools</strong></li>
</ul>

<p><img src="/assets/images/popular_product_analytics_tools.jpg" alt="popular_product_analytics_tools" />
<em>Some popular product analytics tools</em></p>

<p>There are two groups of analytics tools in use: the classic analytics and the retroactive analytics tools. The tools you use vary based on your business needs and requirements.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Classic analytics captures pageview events by default (page-based) and other events that has been setup to be tracked on the website. It gathers data from the day you implement it. Google Analytics falls under this category.</li>
  <li>Retroactive analytics captures all events happening on-page by default (event-based). Tools in this category automatically collect user interaction data with a single snippet and let you analyze that data when you need to. Examples include mixpanel, heap and amplitude.</li>
</ul>

<p>The difference between classic and retroactive tools is in the…</p>

<ul>
  <li><strong>Step 4: Follow a consistent process</strong></li>
</ul>

<p>What is the key information each team needs to look at weekly?
How do you ensure tracking is in place for new feature launches?</p>

<h3 id="a-typical-product-analytics-stack">A typical product analytics stack</h3>

<ul>
  <li>Segment: to connect all your tools together from mixpanel, Google Analytics to your website and CRM.</li>
  <li>Google Analytics (for marketing analytics), to gather top of the funnel page-view events.</li>
  <li>Mixpanel, Amplitude or Heap to understand what users are doing after signup.</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="reporting-analytics-events">Reporting analytics events</h2>

<p>Reports are time-based and segmented views of product data. They can be shared, updated and embedded or self-created by users. They are visual guides that enable stakeholders understand the performance of the product’s metrics.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Dashboard is a collection of various reports.</p>
</blockquote>

<h2 id="most-useful-reports-in-analytics">Most useful reports in analytics</h2>

<p>The reports used for the below section were generated from Google Merchandise Store Universal Analytics demo account. Visit the <a href="https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6367342#access&amp;zippy=%2Cin-this-article">demo account information page</a> for full details, tutorials and access limitations. Otherwise, you can go directly to the <a href="https://analytics.google.com/analytics/web/demoAccount">Universal Analytics property</a> or the <a href="https://analytics.google.com/analytics/web/demoAccount?appstate=/p213025502">Google Analytics 4 property</a>.</p>

<h3 id="segmentation">Segmentation</h3>

<p>A segment is a subset of your Analytics data. Segmentation helps us to uncover and understand hidden trends within our product. It allows us to break down product analysis by event or user property, such as location or operating system.</p>

<p>With segmentation you can isolate and analyze a subset of data so you can examine and respond to trends in your business. For example, if you segment and realise that users from a particular region are no longer purchasing a particular product in the same volume as they normally do, you can check whether there is a competitor selling same product at lower prices. If this is true, you could respond by offering a discount that undercuts your competitor’s prices.</p>

<p>You can also use information gotten from segmenting your users to know what group of users to target in a remarketing campaign.</p>

<p>See this short but detailed <a href="https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3123951#zippy=%2Cin-this-article">explanation of segmentation</a> from Google.</p>

<h3 id="cohort-analysis">Cohort Analysis</h3>

<p>Cohort analysis helps us to find out which group (segments) of users stay engaged with our product the longest. It also helps us to understand if our product has improved over time. i.e. if newer users are staying longer than older ones did.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/cohort_analysis.jpg" alt="cohort_analysis" /></p>

<p>The above image shows a 6-week analysis of users grouped by <em>Acquisition date</em> and the <em>Total transactions</em> they carried out from their first week (Week 0) to the present week (Week 6).
We can observe that the initial total transactions are high. However, the number of repeat purchase from these users drop rapidly as the week goes by. This drop could be explained by the type of products on the <a href="https://shop.googlemerchandisestore.com/?utm_source=partners&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_campaign=data%20share%20article">Google Merchandise store</a>. These are not FMCG products. So a better cohort size would have been by month or year.</p>

<p>To understand cohort analysis further, <a href="https://medium.com/analytics-for-humans/a-beginners-guide-to-cohort-analysis-the-most-actionable-and-underrated-report-on-google-c0797d826bf4">read this article</a>.</p>

<h3 id="funnel-analysis">Funnel Analysis</h3>

<p>Funnels are used to understand user behaviour usually in a specific order. It shows us data on users who have gone through a funnel we define (e.g. single product, add to cart, checkout, create account, complete checkout). Through this, we can identify user drop-off points to improve conversion rates.</p>

<h3 id="user-flows">User flows</h3>

<p><img src="/assets/images/user_flows.png" alt="user_flows" /></p>

<p>A flow analysis helps us to understand user behaviour in a less structured way than funnels. It helps to understand what events are key to reaching a goal and how users use our products outside how we intend them to use it.</p>

<p>It allows us to see where a user goes/does after a starting point (e.g. next five actions that a user did after visiting the landing page) or what the user did before an ending action (e.g. previous five actions user did before buying our product).</p>

<p>It helps us answer the question: <em>“Where are users going to from event X?”</em> and <em>“How are users getting to event Y?”</em></p>

<h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h2>
<p>As a product analyst, your major job is not just to find creative ways to share insights across your organisation but also finding meaningful ways to empower others to discover insights on their own. To fully take the advantage of data, data blending is a useful concept which is merging data from different sources for analysis. This helps us to see data from different perspectives. Going forward as a product analyst, it is a standard practise to automate reports to help reduce drudgery while improving reliability.</p>

<p><strong>P.S:</strong> This is a summary gotten from the Product Analytics course at CXL Institute.</p>]]></content><author><name>ndcharles</name></author><category term="Product" /><category term="Data" /><category term="featured" /><category term="product_analytics" /><category term="CXL_Institute" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of most products, instincts, gut-feeling, interviews and surveys form the basis of decision making. After developement and people start using the product, data is generated. The available data is then used to validate hypothesis that would help in improving the product. This is when product analytics comes in.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/how-use-data-build-products-that-customers-need.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/how-use-data-build-products-that-customers-need.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/powerful-things-markdown-editor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor" /><published>2019-01-24T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-01-24T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/powerful-things-markdown-editor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/powerful-things-markdown-editor/"><![CDATA[<p>There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor</p>

<p>If you’ve gotten pretty comfortable with writing in Markdown, then you may enjoy some more advanced tips about the types of things you can do with Markdown!</p>

<p>As with the last post about the editor, you’ll want to be actually editing this post as you read it so that you can see all the Markdown code we’re using. oya update it.</p>

<h2 id="special-formatting">Special formatting</h2>

<p>As well as bold and italics, you can also use some other special formatting in Markdown when the need arises, for example:</p>

<ul>
  <li><del>strike through</del></li>
  <li>==highlight==</li>
  <li>*escaped characters*</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="writing-code-blocks">Writing code blocks</h2>

<p>There are two types of code elements which can be inserted in Markdown, the first is inline, and the other is block. Inline code is formatted by wrapping any word or words in back-ticks, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">like this</code>. Larger snippets of code can be displayed across multiple lines using triple back ticks:</p>

<div class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>.my-link {
    text-decoration: underline;
}
</code></pre></div></div>

<p>If you want to get really fancy, you can even add syntax highlighting using Rouge.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/3.jpg" alt="walking" /></p>

<h2 id="reference-lists">Reference lists</h2>

<p>The quick brown jumped over the lazy.</p>

<p>Another way to insert links in markdown is using reference lists. You might want to use this style of linking to cite reference material in a Wikipedia-style. All of the links are listed at the end of the document, so you can maintain full separation between content and its source or reference.</p>

<h2 id="sample-blockquote">Sample Blockquote</h2>
<blockquote>
  <p>Writing good technical articles is indeed a challenge, takes a lot of your personal time and often requires doing a lot of research. Of-course you should have a passion for reading and writing it. Before you write your paper, you need to understand your audience and your message.</p>
</blockquote>

<h2 id="full-html">Full HTML</h2>

<p>Perhaps the best part of Markdown is that you’re never limited to just Markdown. You can write HTML directly in the Markdown editor and it will just work as HTML usually does. No limits! Here’s a standard YouTube embed code as an example:</p>

<p><iframe style="width:100%;" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Cniqsc9QfDo?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></p>]]></content><author><name>ndcharles</name></author><category term="Jekyll" /><category term="Tech" /><category term="markdown" /><category term="editor" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of powerful things you can do with the Markdown editor]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/art_work.webp" /><media:content medium="image" url="http://localhost:4000/assets/images/art_work.webp" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>